Meditation on, if you can lie
but don't know it very well, then you can
record it. Can you put your phone
here in front?
The people in front play deeply.
Here are the ones sitting in the back. It
was, and those in front are, they will be
frozen. If you are not recording,
please turn off your phone. Let's do
a nice, slow, relaxed
dance, and probably a break in
the middle. Some were
n't even here during the country, and that's why
I will include a few explanations.
It will be 90.
Here is paper,
and don't save any
more. Then, during the
meditation,
helpers, go!
The Lion Dance meditation begins by
perceiving some noises in the room, like the air conditioning,
the heating, the refrigerator,
the traffic outside, or children, or
small noises in the room. If you are in
a cabin on Diamond Mountain and
there are train tracks, then you can
use the sound of the air as it
touches your eardrum, and now attach
yourself to this sound.
If you want to meditate for about half an hour
or 40 minutes, then
you can take ten hard drags in each step,
and if  If you
want to meditate for a whole hour, then take
about 20 breaths at each step,
and then come the eight first greetings of
the lion dance, and they always compare
the previous level
with the next, and you always try to become
calmer, and that is also always
a characteristic, meaning you always let go of the loudness of the louder
level and you move to a
quieter level, and it is a very
active, a very active comparison
between the bushes of the air conditioning,
then you go to the first of the realm
level with the beating of the heart, and
you compare that with the content of the
air conditioning, and that means we can,
in comparison and comparison of the louder
with the quieter place, then we
very consciously choose the quieter place and
move into it, so compare
the air conditioning, which is sufficient, which
symbolizes, so to speak, the
rough reality in which we live,
and then we should now go to the quiet
place of the beating heart and
follow the beating of the heart in the first
room, why realm and what is not really realm,
but  If you were to focus
solely on the
beating heart
as a form of meditation, and if
you were to practice this devotedly,
then you would be reborn
in the first realm. This
is very similar to
superheroes like Wanderlust or
Spiderman.
And when this chamber is exhausted,
when this debit card is used up,
then 99 percent of these people will
go to a lower realm.
That's why we don't want to simply
indulge in mindless meditation
without any content.
We don't want to procrastinate, to give ourselves over to
things that work against us, that
they don't come from us.
So now we take the steps so that
it becomes calmer and calmer.
We go up eight floors, but do
n't get off on the first eight
floors. This is
only about becoming calmer,
and this doesn't stop the process of
aging and dying. So
now the beating heart in the first realm,
and then a new spirit immigrates. Furthermore,
instead of air conditioning or a
fan, half of your
spirit should be reattached to the
first format.  Namely, the beating heart
can be used to distract ourselves and
ascend to the next level,
the second of the realm. Here,
we imagine not observing the heart from the outside,
but rather going into the heart.
Technically speaking,
this means going from vital to safe, from
deeper stillness to an even deeper level
of stillness.
Imagine that you are inside the
heart, like in a small room,
and it beats around you. Perhaps
you are even beating with your heart. So go into the heart
because it
is an even calmer place than observing the heart from the outside. With
each step, we go deeper and deeper.
The third form of realm level: here,
we classically let go of any feeling
of attachment or pleasure, or
anything we enjoy. For example,
we let go of the meditation posture
and we distance ourselves from the
beating heart, both physically and emotionally.
And now we see the beating heart,
and it is a little further away from us, as if in
a vacuum. And I no
longer refer to it so much; it is
simply a little further away from me.  My
feeling here is
much weaker, it's almost extinguished.
So imagine your beating heart in
a kind of vacuum, especially an
emotional vacuum. You're
no longer so connected to it.
It's an even deeper stillness than
being in your heart.
The fourth level of the realm is
distinguished by the fact that we
concentrate completely on a sharp focus.
We let go of almost all the sensations in the
body and the good meditation
posture, so that it's almost as if the body is
completely numb. You can no
longer feel it, and the mind
now focuses like a laser beam into
a single point. Classically,
this helps in meditation.
If you now have difficulty
reaching this sharp point,
then imagine something very small
and focus your mind on it. This
helps to focus your concentration.
We use a small sugar crystal. A
single small sugar crystal floats
in darkness, three white, a
beautiful white crystal. Let your
mind wander into it
and let go of your body awareness completely.
These are also not antidotes to  Salsa,
and that won't solve your problems either, your
life problems, neither with
your family - with a job or the
bigger problems of mortality. But
we climb the ladder where we
then dedicate ourselves to these problems.
Now we go to the formless realm
level. If you were to meditate only for extended periods,
then you would be
reborn in a place where there is no
great suffering because you would
n't even have a body and would
live like that for a very long time. And then when you die,
you would always have to descend to the lower realms
because you would have used up
all your karma. And that's why
we don't stay in
this meditation;
we only use it to ascend. And
that means since January,
we simply demonstrate our flexibility
in meditation. We can go from
a single sugar crystal to
another state of mind that extends across the
entire space. So
now we imagine a huge
lake, and our mind is like the
surface of this lake, and that is on
a horizontal plane and extends to the
left and right,
and we let
one  There will be a small stone in the
center of the lake,
and then the lake will ripple. I
like to make just a small wave, about
a centimeter
high, and I've found it's
especially effective when it's very, very
still.
So now it's even calmer and even deeper. Even deeper, these are
sugar crystals. But we're now showing off
our mental flexibility, from
a single sugar crystal to
the expansion of the entire universe, and we'll still become
citizens. So drop the
stone
and let the CT spin. And that doesn't happen
when you lose focus. It's
back to the cooling effect, and follow it to
the horizon. And there's no
shore.
Then come back to the center of your
mind.
For me, it's very dark, like
a place in the middle of a room,
about two meters above the floor.
Come to the center of the mind, and
now we're going to an even calmer
place, which is the second
level from the loose end. And now we're going to
imagine we're turning on a light, and
the light is flying from the lightbulb.  In the
form of a sphere that
expands ever further, and this light
is not white or yellow, but
completely clear. As I said, this isn't
the meaning of clear light in
Buddhism,
but it's simply a crystal
color, and that's not the meaning
of clam light in Buddhism.
But we don't imagine a crystal
expanding from a single point in the form of a ball, a sphere,
as large as the earth. And I would like to see it
expanding beyond the sun, beyond the stars.
The universe has countless planets and
stars. There
are also people who
meditate now, just like us in
countless places, who meditate now,
also on the second, formless, high plane.
And I like to imagine
my Christa light, whose light survives, and
how it somehow touches, and
perhaps one day we will
even be able to consciously experience this.
And if I say now, then turn on
this light and let this crystal
light expand endlessly in all
directions like a ball.  And this light
is your own consciousness, it's free, turn on
the light,
that's not stopping the test, on
and on, and at the same time
try to be still inside, still,
the lake has
the third gateless realm level, that it's the
seventh of eight if you
call the air conditioning zero, and that's
now called Schirmer, and we
simply imagine that we turn off the mind
like a switch, no thoughts, no
feelings, no consciousness, just
dark, black, as if your mind had
died,
and when I say go on,
turn off the mind, then thoughts, feelings,
memories come, then push aside
that the mind is simply turned off,
a deeper stillness than the level
before, when the mind has spread out,
the fourth harmless realm level, that
is the highest of the eight
meditations we use to
prepare our mind for the true
meditation,
because these are all not the real
situation,
that is only, so to speak, a din and
warming up of the mind before the real
meditation, these are not the
real meditations, they cannot help you,
at least not in a true way,
they cannot  Your life doesn't help
on the fourth formless realm level,
the mind is still switched off,
but when thoughts come, memories,
feelings, then we surrender to them,
simply and we go through the mind,
and we don't make the noise to
stop them.
They will be the MQ, gone by, the ones who do it,
and now this is
therefore an even quieter place where
we simply surrender.
We switch off the mind, but if it ca
n't be switched off, then
we simply let go. So, in
complete silence
now, without your eyes,
three deep exhalations,
then you can gently open your eyes
and stretch.
Microphone, are there
any questions about this
part?
This is the first part. We'll start
the second part right away. But are there any questions
about the first part?
Thank you. I have a question: when we
move from one form to another, when
we go from one woman to another, do
we stay in the one while
we go to the next? So, Dennis, ask
here: when I give the
instruction, should we
go to the next one right away, or should we wait?
If you do this for a week,
then you can use these instructions,
but after that you can...  You
use this recording, and then
you simply decide quickly. It
's always a form of
comparison, so the level is set
here, and then he says, "I can go
even faster," and then look
ahead to your next step and tells you that it would be even
quieter. And there should
even be a feeling of "I'm going
deeper here." For me, it feels like
I'm drilling myself deeper. Then, when
I'm still sitting down,
I get used to
the place, and then I think, "Now I'm going even deeper,
now I'm going even quieter."
You're just imagining
that you can go beyond the realm of the publisher,
and before you actually get to a
formless realm meditation, that takes a
long time, but he's just imagining it for you.
And so you will
go deeper and deeper, and the truth is,
Ivo is very, very calm and still,
but you have to
train for that first. You have to practice it.
That takes a while. Life is
really about practicing every day. We've
done about an hour now,
and even if you can't do an hour every day,
you can still get through it
faster.  The levels go,
we have to go to work, and then
you just take five breaths per
level. And if I say five breaths at the beginning,
then count to 5 and
then do it, and then continue. But afterwards,
you don't count anymore.
Later, there's one with 25 minutes, 10 per level, which
is half an hour and 20
breaths, that's about an hour.
So first, you use your breath and count,
and afterwards, of course, you have to let go of that
because it
's also a distraction.
My mind thinks about things instead of
being calm, so it's always agitation.
Especially in the first 80 minutes, I have the
tendency that
we're not supposed to think, but that goes
against my tendency. So, for example, in the
calm one, I was very distracted. Very
often, when I finished this meditation,
I was quite tired because I had exerted
myself so much, and that
's not exactly very peaceful. My
mind is constantly thinking about things
and analyzing things. How would you
suggest I do it differently? Well,
the human mind is simply very
active.  And Stanley is very active, much like
me, and getting the mind to listen to
you is also
a struggle. Who wrote the best
meditation books? Kamlah,
China. How many books? Three books, called
Werner Kramer in Sanskrit and
Bomben in Tibetan. And we
read them together here, in the first two
chapters, L'Aquila,
and there's nothing in them that you'll find in the
country. Because of this,
in these books
they say it's very, very typical that
these students go to the teacher and
say, "After I learned about meditation,
my mind has gotten much worse. You
were already sometimes quiet, but
now when I think of the animals, it's even
worse than before."
And then there was Werner Kramer, and then
this manual about meditation says, "Your
mind was always terrible, but you
just didn't know it,
and now you'll turn your mind to it, and
now you know how bad it is."
And that's roughly how it is for the first six
months when you're frustrated, when you
think you're getting worse and
worse,
then you will  Then you learn to
listen to your mind for the first time. That's
how bad it is, and it's not like it was
always this
bad. You were both involved, which doesn't mean you just picked up on listening.
Now it's about listening to the mind,
otherwise you'll always be busy thinking, thinking, thinking.
And now, when you observe this, you
think your mind is getting
worse, but now you're simply learning to
observe your mind for the first time, and then you learn to
control it.
But there is, so to speak, a phase
where you actively fight the mind,
and my suggestion, just so it doesn't get discouraged, is to
quickly go to number 8
and then quickly to number 9.
Because, so to speak, the method is
that it quickly goes through number 8 to get to
new things, or the mind is like a colorful, bad
dog, and he has the
dog on a leash.
We sometimes have a small dog,
never, and I have a small black
dog, and he always wants to go.
He's so small, but he pulls and
pulls on the leash, and then he had to
Because now, pulling, and the dog—in
my case, the dog is always thinking about
lunch, the
last argument with Iron Man, or whatever
someone on the internet said—
so this dog always goes away, and you always have to
tell it to come back,
and then it stretches out for a while like
the little black dog, and
then it thinks, "That's something
different again," and you have to pull it back again.
And every time you pull it back,
this muscle here gets
stronger and stronger. In Buddhism,
striving and fighting is a
good thing, and that is, of course, actually
exhausting. And if the dog is
called my mind, then it's just
super exhausting. Epaper did 23 consecutive
retreats,
and you can ask her. So,
for example, they came to me, and then for the
first time in three years, they came into my
hut, and they said to me, "
Kessler, it looks just like me here,
so peaceful." Yes, I said, "Just like
the Vietnam War.
So many wars were fought
here in this hut." So do
n't think that meditation, like I do, is...  If you
do it wrong, then it
might be peaceful, but if you
truly observe your mind, then
it's a struggle.
You don't feel peaceful right from the first day, like you do
now. Can someone here maybe
turn off their alarm?
You have to fight, and every moment
you fight with your mind,
you make progress.
And if you simply experience space,
dream time, like I do, in empty space,
everything is beautiful, I don't need to think about anything, there are
names for that,
and that's so to speak, subtle
inertia. If you
meditate for longer than you have the capacity, then
you typically slip into this inertia.
If you're a beginner,
you should start with twelve minutes.
That's an old tradition in
Buddhism, Frank, start with twelve minutes,
and then you can maybe go to 20
minutes. But if you
want to sit there for two hours right away, you'll
definitely end up like Jagger Tango. So, that's
this space-time mental not clear
and sharp. What does true
meditation feel like?
I always say it's like when you
watch a good movie, it doesn't matter,
and when you watch the movie and at  At first,
it's very simple: the green
woman, the foreskin, the people,
and the tall ones take care of
the others, and the good-looking ones, then they take care
of the others, and the
short ones. And then there's the point where
her popcorn is there, and then you wait
for that special moment when
the green woman kisses the handsome young man. For
two hours, there's
support, at least in America, and then suddenly
they get close, and
everyone stops eating popcorn, and
everyone is like, maybe
after two movies, they finally kiss, getting closer
and closer, and everyone is like that, and they've
completely forgotten about the popcorn, and that's the
focus, this moment. 200, 300 people are like that, the
feeling. So, in a
good meditation, it's like that. So, it's not like that.
99 percent of all people are like that.
True meditation is clear, but happily
engaged, yes, now the course is coming up.
If you do it like that, by the way, it's
a bad habit. So don't
meditate for too long, 20 minutes,
then stretch as you have been
doing it. If you get stronger, then
do it longer, but if he  If you
make it too long right from the start, it will become
a bad habit. Are there any
other questions?
This is from someone in Vancouver.
My question is, sometimes when I
meditate, I see things
that are very, very frightening, but
they  They are so terrifying that I
even have to take a break, and
how am I supposed to do that? Should I
take a break, or what am I supposed to do?
She is her own apartment. Three goes
meditation, and SC 1, number three
also goes about meditation, and the great
breakthrough
that NTC made to Qatar, the great
that the body made, is in
a letter that he wrote to one of
their students, which is called "You are
grateful," and that is also in the three main
paths, and in this letter he
said
meditation is seeing what goes out into a mind.
Every time you hear your thoughts,
then they open up.
That's what we'll do next in
this meditation. Little thoughts
come from a mind, and you are
not the thinker, you are the listener. So
if you have thoughts in your
mind all day,
then you are only the witness. You are
not the speaker. The speaker
left the room for about a certain amount of time.
I always like to say that it's like light
from a star, the light you
saw from the star. That was beautiful last
night when guests were there after the
new moon.  The light left the star
about a year ago, ten years ago,
or 100 years ago, and by the time the
light reaches your eye, the star may have gone out,
the star may have become ocean. Your
thoughts are the same; when you
hear your thoughts, the speaker has
already disappeared. So
you can't control them,
you can't control the speaker,
that's impossible.
I like the translator of my lamer, and
then people came, and his English
had to be translated into English, and
then the people came. I am, I am
always so depressed, always so depressed,
and then I translated that, and then
he says in the budget,
I have some advice for you.
Sometimes they come from far away, and
then he says, and then you tell
him, you should be happy,
and then he made his proposal again,
and then that means, as well as, that
's now over, the interview, and
then we waited, is there anything else you
want? Are you still here? So
they have a serious problem, they
might kill themselves.
No, I already told them what to do:
be happy. And then
the person leaves again, and they are
quite angry.  depressed, and then
I go back upstairs to the vampire
and say, "Why? You just told him to be
happy and didn't give him any
advice,
and then you tell me it's too late. The
seed is opening now, the higher ones, to a star that has
already gone out.
It's too late.
You'll be depressed today because if
you're not depressed next week, then
be—that's all there is to it. Plant well
together this week, this week. When
you hear the seeds,
then beautiful things will happen. And in
meditation, it's the same:
you can't reduce it, because you ca
n't control your mind at the moment.
You're listening to what's
coming, and maybe you have something calm,
and maybe it's something loud.
But when you hear it, then it's too late.
You can't... The one who
invented personalities said you ca
n't push a tree back into the earth.
The true key
to meditation is not to disturb other people's minds, make
other people
happy, make other people feel good,
and be kind to them. And next
week, when your seed sprouts,
then it's...  A good thought, but if you
hear the thought, then it's already too
late.
The true key to meditation is
not to disturb other people's minds. Be kind
to other people's minds,
which makes them happy and peaceful,
and next week your mind will
be peaceful.
So, if very strange,
frightening images come into your mind,
then it's too late to
stop them.
So, if the light
has reached your eye, then you can
no longer speak to the stars because
the SR
learns to clear, the four powers to
purify bad seeds. And be very
careful not to
frighten or scare other people. And if
these thoughts come, then it
means that you have
no more time.
Okay, so now we'll do the second
part of the meditation.
Grab your things, it
's the second part of the release dance,
and then take a bathroom break.
You can go to your nose, it could be
military. We won't
do it for too long.
So, we'll now pretend that we've just come
from the fourth formless
realm level situation.  And when the
thoughts came, we didn't really
perceive them. We were in true
meditation, namely on the ninth
floor. The first eight floors,
including the ground floor, are not true
meditation
because they don't contradict how
our mind normally draws our world.
Now, bring one of your teachers for you.
This could also be your father and mother,
or a first-grade teacher.
Many of us had
sports teachers to whom we feel drawn.
This could be a spiritual
teacher, like a priest, or a mentor,
or a person. Many of us
also had teachers in our profession, and
we learned a lot from them.
Or we can also think about a
historical teacher, like Jesus Muhammad. A
teacher of the heart is a
special image of things. Believe that
he or she has helped you more than anyone
else. We call this a
teacher of the heart.
For some of us, if we haven't met one yet,
the opposite of whom we don't yet
have this feeling,
then you can imagine a perfect teacher of the heart.
And now bring
this teacher to you.
He or she is sitting in meditation right in front of you.  And this
is the beginning of encouraging you
to visualize this teacher very, very realistically.
It's not a concept, this is not a
picture, this is not a statue, it's a
breathing, warm, living person, a teacher
sitting knee to knee in the middle, the room
closed, their eyes
open, looking where I have
mentioned with great love. I am very happy
that you are meditating.
There are many qualities that he
admires in your heart's teacher, and of
course, there are many qualities that
we ourselves would like to develop, and that is why
they are our teachers.
In this meditation, at this level, focus on
just one quality, one quality
that he loves in this person. It
could even be something you know.
I even knew someone who
said that a teacher was like his dog,
and I believed him. So think
about a good quality that
you admire in this teacher. You
can change the teacher every day,
or you can also
stay with the same teacher for days
and then switch. As you
do this meditation more and more,
you will discover more and more sweet qualities
of the teacher.  I find it's not
particularly
good if you focus on a negative quality in
a person and
meditate on it, because that doesn't elevate a
mind; it doesn't make you a
better person.
So I encourage you to
choose an admirable quality from someone else
and focus on that.
Now, choose a quality.
Now go back to the center of your
mind where we meditated for a while.
I imagine a dark room,
and in the center of the room, imagine
a small nest, a small
bird's nest, and in it, six or
seven beautiful silver eggs, as
if a target is aimed at them.
They are very, very shiny and beautiful.
Now imagine that one of these eggs
breaks open, and an image comes out—a
luminous, shiny little image, about
the size of a marble. And this comes out of
the egg like a hologram.
This is the image of the quality of your
teacher, and in my case, let's say
the respect that Mine Lama
gives to others. So, I think that now a
silver egg, not in the center of your
mind, and out comes an image of the
respect that you give to everyone else,
and that...  It now moves towards
destroying my mind, and then
it comes out of my head, and then
this image settles over my lama like a
cloak, and that feels like my lama, and
then my lover is enveloped in the
attention that is then given, and if
you get nervous in meditation,
then you can think that the seeds,
then you can imagine them more, so to speak,
at navel level, at the back of
the spine, and then
you are more grounded.
The feeling that you see in your teacher,
the beautiful quality that you see, in
my case, this attention, the
coming of seeds in my mind that
make images, and these images
settle over my lama, and the goodness, the goodness
that I see in my lama
comes from these together, think about it,
then go back to the second one. It wants to break it open, it breaks it
as the image
comes out, it wants to lie over the lama,
and that is the second moment, that is how
the attention is, I see it, and then go back again,
and again this process happened for a few
minutes. In real life, this happens
65 times a second.  So, a second opens up,
we'll just slow this down.
If you do this part correctly, then
you should have a shocking feeling
because the beauty I see in
my teacher, the swimming instructor,
comes from me. I may
not see this quality in myself yet, but I have
seen it in another person.
And now we're going on a little fun
journey, namely, what did I do
to plant these seeds? I must have done
something so that I see these
things, so that I see this quality in my
llama. I must have planted them together. So, I could have been
in this life now,
but we're going to imagine now, pretend we're going back to
our past lives,
and we're going to imagine something
we did in our past lives, putting them
together,
planting them. So be creative, be
happy. There were
beautiful things you
did in your past life,
really very beautiful habits. You had them for
many years, like other people. Be
creative, don't get stuck, just take
any image that comes up
because all these images belong to you,
that some story, some
story that comes about
past lives, that comes from your
saying.  That might not be exactly
right, that might not be exactly
what happened.
Sometime in the future, you will be able to
see your life directly, see past
lives directly. But now
let's just describe a film
about past lives. What honor was it?
Maybe 100, 400 years ago, or
1000 years ago, was I in China or India,
rich Europe? Was I an Indian, and did
I never treat people? What did
I do every day to plant this, to
plant such a considerate llama? Just
a few breaths, and then we'll
pause.
Now come back to your llama, back to you,
and now you have a better feeling about
why you ask this quality, and with great
respect, to step aside.
And now imagine this is
another picture of your llama that
looks just like the llama, but this is now
two of the same. The man in the kitchen,
this second conceited llama, whose
good quality doesn't come from me, doesn't come
from my seeds.
I didn't deserve it.
It's not because I treated other people.
It's just a
coincidence, an accident.
This time, I simply encountered this lama by
chance. They didn't come
from me. There's
no history between us in
the past. There's no
past life from when I
planted them or met them. There's
also no future between us,
like a grand, beautiful ending to this
story. There are
no future lives together. There are
no past lives and
no future lives, and no media
either, not even for enlightenment. Together, it's
just an accident.
I simply met them by chance.
I came here by chance.
They came here by chance.
And if you continue with this kind of thinking,
then everything is just coincidence.
I only meet people by chance. So there are
no past reasons for it. Even
the universe only came about from a
random explosion. We experienced the
distress,
and then small dust particles collided with
each other because
billions of years ago they met,
and then my
nose was created, and my teacher's nose and
eyes.
Man created this world, and it's
all just a huge coincidence,
and I call that  This, I like to call this
lama, probably the random
lama, the Big Bang, and now try to feel this, it
's outrageous, so I
think it's outrageous, my exquisite
dear lama, it's not a Big Bang
and it's not a coincidence,
it's not true that we don't have a
happy future together, we
have spent many past lives together,
they come from these wonderful
sayings, and I resist this
idea that this is just a random lama,
I don't believe it,
and then push aside, push aside
this false random lama
and bring back the true lama,
and be aware that the place where the
true lama is placed, the false
lama has now been crossed out,
and this is instructive, without majority
I cannot see this lama as he
comes from seed, so practice this feeling
that your life, the lama, sweet lama, that
he exists, and indeed in this place that remained
when we crossed out the random
slammer,
that is our name, as he lives in majority,
and then, three times long,
then open your eyes  And
I stretched, answering questions after this 15-minute break.
I think there are some wonderful
green drinks and fresh juices for you
in the kitchen. I encourage you
to drink a green drink. In
my opinion, the green drink is
right under yoga. I don't like either,
but if you
drink one, then you'll have
a good class. Okay, so just hold your
nose and get it
down in 15 minutes until dancing. Okay,
we're going back to the verse now,
to dancing at the end of the diamond cutter. We
have about another hour now,
and at the end of this hour, we'll go
over the schedule for
meditation day. Day, the day he
died at the depot, Maja.
We're now at character, so star.
We've said that there are six
different meanings, and I'm going to
repeat here that
the first one is that it's the first
meaning of camera, China, and what
you like, lama, and yes, me, and that says
that the stars can only appear in the dark,
and in their
understanding, it's like this: we see the
object  Not understanding
that the star means that
bad things are in our lives
because we don't understand them,
and if we did understand,
they would go away like the
sun rising. We always use
this example, not just for men, but
also for women. Women sometimes cause
trouble too. So, if
you texted your children last week,
and then you come home and a
man is yelling at you for
no apparent reason at all, then
you have two choices.
You can either
understand that it's coming from your little ones themselves,
the llama, or you can think you haven't done anything at all
and they're just
hurting you. And if you think you haven't done anything at
all,
that's like darkness, and
then the man is like a star, and then
he will hurt you.
We should, of course, change our selves.
You don't even have to say
that he changes them; there's
no need for a long
discussion. You can simply
change them. And that doesn't mean he
should let someone hurt or be
taken advantage of. If someone hurts you,
you don't have to just stand there
and say...  These are simply my things, there's
nothing you can do. You can,
you can take action, for example, leave,
or you can get
advice, even legal help.
You have to understand, but
you have to understand that whether all of this works
depends on your own actions.
So there shouldn't be any hat involved.
I will therefore leave; I will seek
psychological or
legal help. You can do that,
but here, for example, in Diamond
Mountain, they sign a document
every time they come here: no
weapons, no alcohol, no drugs, no
injuring other people or
sexually harassing other people, or anything like that. That has been
the rule here for about ten
years. And if something happens here,
and if you, so to speak, if
something happens here, then
you should contact the board.
These are the members of the
board. So
if you have a problem with someone,
then go to the board here.
And then, if you are shy,
you could, so
to speak, report it anonymously.
And we have a system here for
how we follow up on these things, and
I was at all these meetings, and we actually  We've
already
persecuted people here, or rather,
we've already disciplined people and even
reported them. So
if you have a problem here, please let
us know.
And if you have a problem from the past,
you can still tell us. But do
n't forget the stars that
come from you. You can
report it to the board, but you
caused it, and you don't need to get angry.
You just need to
change it, so to speak. The
second meaning here is that the
stars represent suffering.
And if the sun rises now, and what does it
mean to see the teachers directly,
then that can't have anything to do with envy.
They can never again
collect chambers for light.
They may still have old chambers,
but they don't create new chambers
to be reborn.
And then there's another
meaning, namely that the majority, that
only the teachers of Haiti allow things to
appear. So here,
the darkness isn't what we
know now, but it's the
learning period.
We
removed our random lama from our meditation, like...
For example, a white screen—
simply erase the random llama,
and that creates space for the true
llama from the projector. The project is
the mind. So now, to concentrate,
here means the darkness, the empty space,
and only this empty space allows the
thing to appear.
So, the darkness allows it.
Now think of a white film screen,
and that is the majority, and your mind
is the projector.
And if there were no majority,
then there would be no things. So, if there were
no dark space, then
the stars couldn't appear anywhere.
And now we come to the third
meaning.
That's why in the first meaning,
darkness is... So, in the first meaning,
is it a good thing or a
bad thing? That
is darkness—what is good or
bad? No, darkness is the
misunderstanding, that is nothing
good. You can... Would you consider darkness
as something good or bad?
Think about it, because the misunderstanding
here is something bad, and then the
star is the second man, the distance before one,
but it could also be said that the
darkness is something good, namely the
majority of the canvas, and that is something good,
and that is now the fourth
meaning of the star and the
darkness.
You can think that the darkness
is something bad, but it is something good.
One will now go deeper, because this
is the majority of the darkness.
Yes, it sounds beautiful to some people and
terrible to others, and the
darkness can therefore be the misunderstanding,
or the darkness can
be the majority that allows things to
appear at all, and that would now be
the fourth meaning. The fifth
meaning now comes from someone, an
Aja, namely Magath. He is so famous
that he is sometimes called the second brother. He
is one of the very first
great Ajas, and when we
come to the end here with Com na China,
we study his third
book, Wisdom. Of course, people have
given him a much longer name,
which is the appointed one.  The book, namely
wisdom, four of us, 27 chapters, all in
verse form, wonderfully beautiful, and that
is truly it would be like bringing a ship into
the house, rich undertakings, all the teachings
about the apprenticeship in China,
in Tibet, in India, in the couple, and then
Japan, it all comes from the garden of
this book here, so you will be well
entertained.
I believe that it will take us two or three years
if we go through this. I
have never seen a good translation of it.
The gardener wrote many poems
but also many commentaries.
For example, Samantha Bad was there, there is
a device and instruments,
the prayer is the typical, the most
typical gift is that the sky
is covered with many flowers, and that is
part of Lammert about and of the German
meditation song, and he
wrote a commentary about this
famous prayer, and he then
wrote how the stars appear in a glass
when you go out in your eyes at
night, and then and then and then
and then, when you have a bucket
full of water, and when you see the
stars then in  Reflected in this bucket of water,
then he says Nagata,
then the meaning of the stars is
illusion, the meaning of the star is
only illusion.
You can see a star in a
bucket of water, but it's not the real one.
Then this
style guide app on mobile phones can die, and
if you point it at the bucket, then
nothing happens.
But by the way, if you want to download the Sky Go
app, then you can
see the stars here and also
the history of these stars.
That was number five, Magath. So he says
the star is illusion.
Here you can see all the stars in
water. Number 6, that's
just common sense, so to speak.
That's simply
that stars are visible for about twelve hours,
that they are 60. The sixth
meaning is, so in permanence, the
stars always go away. One of the most
famous questions about this verse is, is
he talking about in permanence,
transience, or is he talking about
illusion? Because some of these new
metaphors seem
to speak quite clearly about transience,
and some speak
About religion, and there's a huge
question: for 2000 years,
brother, is it about transience or
illusion?
How would you decide?
Yes, we vote for both. Yes, I agree. Yes, I'm sorry,
but it's true, it's
both.
Every morning the stars disappear, like
our relationships, like our money, our
lives, our bodies. They come
and go, they
are also illusions, and this
illusion naturally depends on
darkness. We don't understand this. Now, to
appreciate this, let's take
meditation number 20. So,
we start at the end.
Now, how many examples do we have? We have three,
so the first three of the new
examples.
Now we've gone through 23 meditations,
and that's only a
third.
Maybe you should stay here for a few months.
So, these are the stars of the
dark night.
This is now the Sanskrit theme. There are
three roots, Tim. One
root, M1, is darkness in
Russian.
So, you see the root here in
Russian, TM, dark.
This means something like blindness.
You can  Not seeing is dark, and
the second is "am," which means something like being
cut off, and a place in a
village, but it's cut off from the rest of the village
because it means a temple,
so "temple," comes from a different
root. So it's cut off
from the village. What do you call a part that can
no longer be divided, that you can't cut off an
atom? So that comes from the root "cut off."
And then there's a third root of "
tam," which is like being afraid, so
shy. It comes from the theme and means,
so I am alone, I am blind, I
am cut off, and I am afraid.
And that means, so to speak,
a cataract in the eye. There is, so to
speak, more skin on the eye,
making one blind. Now I'll give
you six different
meanings for the cataract here, six
different meanings for this.
Look at one eye. It came to China, so
Bandelow, the beautiful Lama Damian Chapa, who
say that the main meaning is that
you think that something is there that isn't there
because of this knot on your
eye,
then you see something that isn't there.  Outside, it's
just a
small bump on your eye, so to speak.
The second husband,
it looks like he's out there, but
that's actually your
own problem. And that's the most famous
interpretation of this
cataract,
and they always divide it into two
different kinds. The first
meaning is that it's always divided into two parts:
you see people and you see
things that aren't there.
The man belongs to the group of people,
but for example, traffic, traffic jams—
someone called me,
I'm going to be late, and then
they said, besides the preparatory course, a
traffic jam from Tucson to the
offspring. Could tell me in Shanghai
or Berlin, but not in
Peer Steinbrück, think of
a better excuse next time. Where
traffic jams come from, also from you. Do
n't get angry about traffic jams.
The reason we study the diamond
cutter is so we
stop getting angry about things.
It's just a kind of bump on your
own eye.  Don't get upset about
things that come from you. Second
meaning:
here it's about the truth of suffering.
I also like to call it the fact
of suffering because it's about suffering
itself. So it's about the four
facts: only if you have a defective
instrument can you see suffering in
life. So
he refers to these eye problems as the truth of suffering.
But someone like Aria can't
see suffering because they don't have a defect in their eye.
And here's the fact
of suffering: this kind of stick on
the eye. And if you didn't have this stick,
then you couldn't
see suffering at all, because he doesn't see suffering, while
the teachers see it directly. The third
meaning:
and he said, let's talk about
Temple Kitty, so entering the Middle
Way. What is the Middle
Way to paradise? Entering the Middle
Way?
Who can tell me that? Because it's
the book
Sandra Katy, his most
important book, from 1400 years ago, at
the Avatar brand. And here
the Middle Way means wisdom of  The
title of his book, "Engagements," is in his
book,
and he talks about a very famous
example from earlier times that
comes from you. So, for example, an example: when
Michael showers, even if he's already
showered before, you can
see that because there are still hairs on the marble. And,
tactically speaking, some
people have, so to speak, a scratch on their eye,
and they always try to clean the shower,
but there's
no hair there, it's just the
scratch on their eye. And with this
scratch on their eye, you will see
what you hate to sow,
and that is the first law, that like
comes like, like comes banana,
and say, what do we have but a
watermelon?
So, what this stick on your eye
makes you see is what you
did recently. You see a hair
on the porcelain because it leaves a
long scratch on your eye, and you
see a screaming man
because your last week...
The scratch on your
own eye will
be exactly the same as what you yourself did.
The content of the illusion comes from how you
treated people last week or last month. Does he understand? Do
you understand? The type of knot on
your eye will determine
what you will see if you have
written to or hurt someone.
Next week, the aha! The hair
you will see in the bathtub is just
a kind of scratch on your eye, and that
is identical.
That is the first law of karma, and
that is the important thing. So, if you
are talking about a defect on your eye, then
you will see exactly the same thing,
almost exactly the same as how you behaved last week. There are
no coincidences.
It is always exactly what you did.
If you had told your children
how beautiful they are last week, what would they
say if you, when you
come through the door, said
you are so beautiful? Is that also a
scratch on your eye? Yes, exactly.
Good answer.
Meaning number four and...  This is
important for "could"
and that means confirmation.
What if a person without a scratch
on their eye comes into the room?
They then come into the same room with clear eyes.
Here, you come into the room, you opened the door,
and your husband said you
're stupid and for no apparent reason. Did
he say that? And then your friends come,
and he just came back from Kamala, China,
and they say,
and then they will be happy, saying, "How will it be?"
If I don't see anyone, yes, there he
just called me Dom.
I didn't do anything! And then they
say, "Why, model booths were created? I don't
see anyone, yes, yes, there he is,
I see
nothing!" Do you understand that someone who
understands the man Schneider Sutra and
comes into the kitchen right after you, who does
n't see a second husband,
understands, yes, that someone without the scratch
on their eye, and they are in the same kitchen and
sees no man who didn't do anything?
Yes, that's called confirmation, the fourth
meaning of the scratch. No, they will
then say there aren't any hairs there,
but that's just a scratch on
your  Eye,
that's called confirmation that you
're crazy. A slightly crazy
person who
comes into the apartment at the same moment. I don't see anyone who doesn't come
from you. And hundreds of times, every time
I've interviewed people, we've said, "
Yes,
we had a problem," and no one listened to
us.
I've interviewed hundreds and hundreds of people, and we've
answered questions. And maybe I'll
turn on a tape recorder, and it
will always say, "Maybe that
comes from me." And I can say I've
spoken with thousands, and the
stories are almost always the same.
These people know the four laws, but my
husband is completely different.
So, for example, I don't have a
scratch on my eye. I have different
scratches on my eye than you do. I can give
you advice, but this is
the important thing: a crazy person
speaks to a non-crazy person.
Then I'm crazy, and they're not
famous. They don't have a scratch on their eye.
I don't know what
you have with your husband. No, he's
really not good. Maybe I understand
that other people are downright...
But I don't have it, and that's called
confirmation. And how much do we have now
for the cataract? Now we go to number
five, so what change? Do
you know what was said when? Think about the
Wheel of Life, how long he
thinks about the Wheel of Life,
namely with the lion's dance, he says,
do the lion's dance, and then go
directly to the Council of Readings. That's the
coolest part. So we first say that
with dependent origination, the seed will
sprout, and then generally speaking,
in the Council of Life, everything is mixed up.
The twelve parts are all suffering, and
the wheel is about the causes of death,
and the whole wheel is
held to the place of death. And Master, what when you
say, if your equipment, your eyes,
but only in your nose, new mind, if
they had been created by chambers,
then they are defective, and that's
interesting because your telescope has a
scratch.
Telescope, so your eyes, your noses, your
ears,
they are equipped with a scratch.
A normal person cannot
think about anything and make a mistake.
That is  Simply saying that's how
your equipment is equipped, there's
always a scratch on it. The
natural human condition is to
always misunderstand things.
It can only be fixed with massive, massive
perfection of wisdom.
Can these factory defects be fixed? When
you came out of your mother's house,
you were already defective.
Even your nose, ears, and nose—they're
all born out of ignorance.
A normal person without training has to
see the wrong things. If they
only use their own eyes, then
it's not just part of the wrong
thinking, but the whole equipment is
defective.
You can't see it any other way than that it
comes from within. Normally,
when you come out of your mother's house,
then five years later
you think it comes from within. And the same
is true for lamb cookies. And
this tastes as if there's
sugar in the cookies and the
sweetness comes from you, but your
tongue will lie to you because your
tongue was born out of ignorance.
The tongue thinks the cookie is  Sweet, but
the sweetness isn't in the way; rather, the
sweetness comes from you. Your equipment is
simply broken, and that was meaning
number five. Now for the good
news number six: that's not all.
Only bad news number six: you have to
learn this, and Adam and Eve Nowotny
means that this is part of your mind
that cannot be removed. It
's already so widespread that if it were
removed, you would
die. So, if you have cancer so severe
that it's already
installed everywhere, then it's simply too
late to operate.
It's already spread everywhere; it
can no longer
be removed.
And that's a hooray!
This is already full of metastases. The
cataract on your eye has already
metastasized; it can no longer be
operated on. And "labor war" means that it's on top of the eye,
and if you
have a good surgeon, it could be
operated on.
So, the good news is that
it can still be operated on. The sixth
meaning is that the cataract is
not yet a part of you but can be
removed.  It will be,
it still hasn't, there aren't any
metastases yet,
so if you learn and teach very carefully
and make a lot of effort,
then you can still cut it out
and then you will
turn things correctly, there you stand, that's
the six meanings, the
concerns, CDP,
finally, that's where the partners in a
verse, you have to make it into a depot, this
root is easy, the root here is thief,
that means shine, the Pi and how
are interchangeable,
so what comes from the wine, so
really debates, many parents
took, so heavenly gods, Jupiter
comes from there, for example,
the old form is namely Jupiter, it is
the father of light, Jupiter, Jupiter
means the father of light comes,
summoned, Tuesday, the Lord comes, to
stay, Tuesday-deep, that which is also the
sky god, the appearing god, the
words wine, sky,
divinity of Jupiter, Tuesday, all
come from this same word, which means
a shining, shining lamp, how
many meanings are there  Here too, number 6, the
first one is back again, China tour, lama,
they say the same thing again: to make a butter
lamp like this one,
you need two things, then you need
the wick, and then you need something, and
then you need the oil or the wax
or the butter. You need two things to
make a lamp,
so you need a push, and you need some kind of
gasoline.
Someone has to multiply that beforehand, and the
fire is yours, but be conscious, but
a misunderstood consciousness, me, that's already
perfect from the
factory, the light, the consciousness that
you turn on in the formless realm, number two,
this light, and this lamp,
is he conscious, and what nourishes that,
namely this substance, this there, and that
means that's the karma, that
represents that, that's where he came from, so this there
is karma, that, or the wax, is
the link, number 8 from the wheel of life,
and what is that when I drink my coffee,
and what is that, so you want,
go, so you want money, so you are
short of money, and someone has money through, and
then you have no  You can choose to
declare it on your taxes or not.
If someone gives you cash for a
service, then you have to pay taxes,
but you think, "Nobody knows that,
I'll just spend the money, I don't want to pay taxes on it."
It's understood
that this attitude, or this
desire,
naturally leads to
understanding where money comes from, and then the desire to
misunderstand that. This
awakens the chamber, which
is the opposite of that. And in a
good seed, what tastes good to the flower seed?
Now, the coffee meditation:
to rejoice that we have done good.
That is the oil, and the
Google together is the wick. And in the
case of a good cadre, it is to
give money there, and the oil is to take
possession of it. I have done that,
I am happy about it. In Windows
meaning, the track is the lamp. The
third example of the new ones is the
fragrance chamber, namely, to
give money generously to others, to one's other people, and the oil is the
compilation, namely, to have the right
attitude. I am glad
that I have performed this good deed.
With these two you get a
fire, and with a bad chamber
it's naturally the same. If your tax is high,
then that's the wick,
and the oil is... I'm glad I did the
right thing. Now I have
more money, and that's the right way
to make money.
They take possession of it, and that's it.
Without that, you can't be
particularly powerful, and without the oil, it
would burn out very quickly.
So the oil is the misunderstanding of where
things come from. Can I continue? Kesha
says, "Let's
connect it with... Let's
connect that with suffering."
He says, "He says that the
material ground is there. That's the thing
that transforms into something else, namely, for example,
the seed becomes a tree, and the stuff
in the hall... Moreover, the
tree shows... and we call that a material ground,
all direct ground, a material
cause. And what are the conditions? That's,
for example, water, fertilizer,
sunlight, and, for example, not
exactly the martens.
He wants to say here that
the material cause is
there because that's where the...  material
cause for the  Fire, and the condition
is that oil, and both mean suffering because that's what
precedes suffering, and
then he says, I think I
discussed this in the middle here.
She has a friend, and her house is
down.
6,000 houses have burned down in California,
and these are very beautiful
houses, and these people can
actually afford insurance very well,
but these
fires are unbelievable. They don't even go
to the ground anymore, they
go from tree to tree,
and that's Apple's number two point to
understand. If you have the material
cause of bad chambers,
if you're glad to have done something
bad, that's the
part of ancient meditation. Yes, yes, I'll do this again
next week. This
bad attitude about their bad deed,
that is, is great, that multiplies
very strongly. On
body day, we
offer something. We put 1,000 under lamps, and that for an
incredibly long time. The daughter from the
small tree world, and then, and
then you do that, and then when you
put them all together, 1,000 together,
then you can very easily create a huge
Beforehand, you always have to
place them very far apart, otherwise it will become a
huge fire and then you can easily
burn down the house, and that's the
meaning here.
I will stop here now
and I would like to briefly
go over your plan for today.
I thought it only went until 10, but
we can continue. So we'll stop
at 10:20 and then
talk about the plan for the day. So, the third
meaning about the lamp, that's a bit more
difficult. When we talked about the
star, we talked about the
background darkness and
then about the light, namely
the star. To see the star,
you need background
darkness so that you can see the star.
And as long as the background is empty,
you can only see things if it's empty.
Only if you have a white screen
can you show a film.
So you have the background
majority, and in Buddhism, that's
called the background, which
is the background, and then the things that
come from the chamber and appear,
and with the cataract, then we
saw things that weren't there at all. We saw
things  who weren't even there,
and when he comes to this, to
the lamp, it's the emphasis on what
appears to you, people and things, what
appears to the lamps, and that's
outside the context of the teacher and
deals with itself, why do I see people, why
them, I think that's
the process of how the silver seeds
open,
and here there's no relationship on the heath
because the word "appear" is the
same in Tibetan as "lamp," what's it
technically called, like Hesse,
that's the false reality because
it's misleading, it looks as if it comes
from itself, where
everywhere, the eyes, the nose, the
ears, they, all these things, they were already
defective from the company, already from the
factory,
no, you weren't sexually active before,
your nose, your nose thinks that it
comes from out there, so to speak, but in
reality, it comes from you, so if you
think someone hadn't showered,
then think again about where that
comes from, for a concert tour, the
third meaning of the lamp is to emphasize
that  Things that come from us,
hair, are the people who
saw the teacher directly in the past.
What is the name for people who did
n't see the majority directly?
Two types are those who
see things come from themselves, and the name for
these people is not, but those who
call themselves that are the ones whose things come back from
themselves.
That's what socom is called. Excuse is therefore from
coming, seeing.
Today, seeing things, it is seeing things come from themselves.
Yes, that is, that is, that it is
difficult, but you like difficult
things, otherwise he wouldn't be here. This
is now again from the garden.
Things are empty, but they function.
Things are empty, but they still
function. If the causes
and conditions are there, then they will
function.
In this, that means the aspirin
tablet. It is called the aspirin tablet.
What is the function of an aspirin
tablet? It is supposed to eliminate headaches.
And what is the name of this substance?
What is the name of the active ingredient in the aspirin
tablet? And what is it called again? Look
in hybrid. That is the chemical name of
this substance, and this  The active ingredient
prevents the pain. The transport box does this.
Here, it's called this chemical active
ingredient, and you can't
trust this Canadian one. It
means it works, but
we say sometimes, sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes it
means the real reason, the true
cause, hasn't been found.
You won't get on a plane
if it only works sometimes. But
he takes an aspirin tablet that
sometimes works and sometimes doesn't.
That means the active ingredient is sometimes
ineffective. You should
call the sometimes effective active ingredient, so to speak. If an
aspirin tablet helps, then what is
actually the active ingredient? Our seeds.
Because we helped someone who had a
headache last week, and you
then saw that it
actually works. Because
the cockpit isn't the
effective active ingredient, but karma is
the effective active ingredient. Does he understand that?
Yes, that's it. So you've now combined the oil
with the
fire, and then it will
work. But it all comes
from you. It's empty.
It's empty of what he... You look at the
bet.  It works
if you are very, very quiet, then I don't
think you understand this,
or okay, these are your things that
make it effective for him.
It is not active without you
activating it, your seeds activating it.
So there is a contradiction between
the lamp and the majority. There is no
contradiction. No, the apprenticeship gives the
lamp a place to exist.
The fire, the fire doesn't burn on its
own; it burns beforehand because you
have the karma.
There are lower schools in Buddhism.
Hot is part of fire, and heat is
part of fire, and wet is simply
water. The higher schools say no.
Who put the mass into the water and
the heat into the fire?
Could you take the wetness out of the water
and march on it if you
had the right seed? Well, we
believe that we believe. Yes, Jesus
also walked on water. He had good seeds. He
talked about seeds for a whole day.
Yes, is there a problem between Christ,
Christianity, and Buddhism? No, I'd say
away. Jesus spoke about it everywhere for a whole day.
So that's all.  A
sign that you have an empty core means
you are simply more successful in
your life: relationships, money,
mental state, the state of
world health—everything comes from you. The
sign that you understand the majority means
you could set things in motion.
It's not like the animals are no
longer the majority;
that's a sign from a person who does
n't understand this majority.
That's a person who understands the teachers; they are so
excited,
and they, like the person in the cinema, and
things are going well, and they know how
things are planted.
So now we have four meanings.
The good things also come from
causes.
So, in Buddhist terms,
if we ever get there,
the causes for Sarah and the
causes for NRW are the
same—all obstacles and
all good things come from the same source: seed,
thought, and fire. And that's
number five:
the good and the bad things
come from your name. And number four
was: things also work even though
they are empty.  Number five was good
and bad things come from the same principle, and in
Buddhist terms we would say condor
means and that advisors, the two
come from the same principle, namely
the ultimatum. Good and
bad come from the same
principle. The
correct pronunciation is his Sarah,
the net, that means nothing. Sarah is called
sansar schanzara.
I would acquire you if you
say star, then you also see his Sarah. That
's not now somewhere, a big wheel
of life somewhere else.
Then tell me the moment in the
church with her second husband. If you
set that in motion with Sarah, then
you set it in motion again, because you hear yourself
when she
comes home next week and the husband says, for absolutely
no reason, he says
to you, "You're stupid." And at that moment
you can either stop the blind man
or you can
set it in motion further
if you say, "No, you're stupid." And then
the children can also be quarreling again next week, so to speak.
And that
Sarah is, so to speak, we do this a
hundred times a day, this wheel of life.
Your reaction to problems is that  Turning the wheel over
and over again,
no, you, you're stupid, and then I don't know
why my children keep
bothering me, the children again, and then
he, my husband, will be closer to me again,
my children again, and that is the red
of Sana'a and also the root of
me, warm in the delusion, because that's the same
principle, and that's the lamp
that Bo
will sing tomorrow, so you
know that you have to be able to pronounce that well tomorrow, can
you do that in the morning to the same
melody, is it bad because that stays in
your head like an earworm,
and when you've heard that once, then
you want to forget it, but you can't forget it,
we do that after meditation because
if you do it before meditation,
then you can't forget it,
that ruins the meditation, and later
someone will say it in Chinese, if
not you, but so teach us a beautiful
Chinese melody that stays in our head,
and then we can learn Sanskrit and
Chinese, how much do we have
now, how much meaning, number 6 comes
now, sixth meaning, and that's
now easy because that costs
Flattered, if there is one, there is
a beautiful metaphor, namely,
we also learn this in school, that is,
life is a candle,
life is a candle, that's a
metaphor and what it means is that it burns
down, you can trust me, I see it
clearly, every minute life burns
down, so the last meaning of
the butter lamp, remember,
life is a candle, every minute it
loses your life, you are
born with one of the cards and your
life is cut short by 65 seeds per second
and that's it, it burns, burns, burns down and down,
and that's pretty
obvious, but nobody
mentioned that here, I then threw in a few
myself, so
we have discussed the first three metaphors
here and they
all relate to how the world around us is, how is it, it's
like a star, what we a
character test, a candle, so we have
the first large group of four
groups,
now we come to the second group and
how many members in the second
group, only one, that's the kind of thing,
Maja Maja and the
root is not clear to anyone, I have
looked up a lot  But nobody knows exactly
what the root is. Maybe it's Maja, which
means something like "to deceive" or "maker." It
's like "much," meaning a great
power to confuse you, like
magnets, cent, or Mahatma,
or like the roots, like "exit," like "
going out," and it could also be "
man," like "to deceive," but
nobody knows exactly.
Sometimes it means "illusion." There are two
main meanings in Buddhism. Illusion
can mean that you
see something, but it isn't actually there.
Classically, when you talk about perception, there's
a cause, namely,
for example, a strong
emotion. If you're very
jealous, for example, you see things that are
n't there. Another thing is
when things move around you.
For example, if you're at a traffic light
with two cars on each side,
and if both of them reverse at once,
then you think you're moving forward
into the intersection.
That's an illusion of movement, and
that sometimes happens. The cars next to you
reverse, and you press the
brake, and at the same time, you're driving...  You don't move forward at all,
and that's called an
illusion of movement, and that's kind of confused.
The second meaning
of Meyer
in Buddhism is the mother of Buddha,
Hiesmayr, and the second meaning is
magic tricks, a magic trick. I
almost used a picture of a
magician who
pulls a rabbit out of a hat,
or he gets a coin
from behind his ear, and that's called a
magic trick. Maja's can also be
called a magic trick. If you drive in the desert and see
water in the
desert from afar, then that's also an
illusion or a magic trick, and that's what
I'll start with tomorrow,
and that's pretty obvious.
I'm going to give you a new meaning of
illusion 9,
because then
we'll discuss what
you're doing today. During the stars, let's
see what's on the schedule.
So, from here, you should have breakfast,
which is a big breakfast for me, and
then from 12:12:15,
you can relax, and to be honest, if you've
slept enough, you ca
n't meditate. Trust me,
it doesn't work if...  If you think
you need to sleep, then he should
sleep. Whenever you think you're
asleep, then he should sleep. When
you get up, then splash
cold water on your face and then
you can meditate. But if you
have jet lag or if you haven't
slept enough, then sleep. Personally,
I do it this way.
I have so many miles. Recently,
the airline
sent me a limo and
drove me from one place to another. I have so many
miles. I always say, don't go
to bed when you arrive, but
stay until everyone else goes to bed, and
then you'll be in rhythm. But if you haven't
slept well,
then you need to sleep. Then, when
you do yoga, first do
water, then God, God
always says, "Is that included with water?" and
12, 15,
and then go through the first three, through
the star, the cataract, and the
lamp.
So you can make a hit list with
six words. When you look,
so in the left eye, that brings
luck, then you see the healthy boat, was
after the bird. They always do it like that.  Knows, that's
probably what the one who looked was
left-wing, so you can
write out six qualities and then
you can look with your left eye, then
you can write down six meanings
and then, if you do, think about something real
in your life, like the star that
is the illusion, namely my husband
who hurt me yesterday. Whenever
you meditate, you should
connect it with your real life,
so don't do it in a philosophical way,
think about people in your life who
are like stars, or think of things that
are empty but still
function, like a lamp or like
from Berlin.
And then at 5:15, by the way, like
Rihanna and I, we will go around and
we will spy on you and then
we will see if you are doing a good
job. But at 5:15,
then enjoy the sunset,
this beautiful thing, and then
also put on a hat and put
sunscreen on it, otherwise it will get
dark spots because both
times, at 12:15 and at 4:00, both of
mine...  Three with six,
so don't do the lion dance all at once,
but first the eight steps
and then the ninth. Tomorrow we'll do
the first two parts of the lion dance
and then we'll come down together.
Today it was just too long,
so between 12:15 and 1:30, and then
also between 4 and 5, you can
warm up with the lion dance, but not by
roaring. And then a
hat and sunscreen, and water—
always water with you. You never go into the
desert without water. I always have a
small bag over my shoulder so my
hands are free. And always keep an eye on a building. I've gotten lost before.
I wandered around for five hours and
couldn't find it. And
I've lived here for seven years! So
it can be dangerous.
Always keep an eye on a building. And definitely don't
stay outside after dark. Snakes, for
example, like the twilight
because mice like the
twilight.
Dusk, when everyone's around
and we're there too, then
you really have to be careful, never
step where you can't see what's
there.
A person who was bitten here once
stepped over a tree trunk and there was a snake
behind it. We have the internet here,
so if something like that happens,
we could come with your help, so to speak.
So relax, if something like that happens,
he gets an injection in the
hospital, but everything's fine. And
if you hear a snake, a
rattlesnake, then don't look for long,
but turn around and don't
look for long. They don't want you to
look at them, they're just
saying to you, "I'm here, I am."
They don't actually want to waste their venom on
you, you're too big. But
if you step on them, then
the flowers will bloom, otherwise not. But
they don't have any, except for humans, who
also mess with snakes. And
then maybe the
lion again at 6
and then 845, can you only
do the Coffee Nation because that's
hopeless for real meditation, and
then always make a list.  What
helped us was a gratitude list. What
helped us starts with your mother
and in your mind, thank them. So,
a huge cosmetic... I
then like to drink hot chocolate
and sit in a very comfortable
chair, or I sit outside and
we look at the stars, and you can also
do mantras. And then
sometimes I lay on my back and looked at the stars
and saw satellites.
But I did millions of mantras on my back
on the roof. And then
put on a sweater and then enjoy
these beautiful stars.
Almost nowhere else will you see such beautiful
stars. We are far enough
away from the city.
The most important thing in the retreat is to be relaxed. Do
n't always smile so easily,
even with yoga if you don't like it, and with
meditation it's exactly the same.
The biggest mistake, and the biggest mistake with both,
is that people
are too strained. So if you are tired,
then take a break.